Guide to the Stanford University Faculty Publications
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Pamphlets and Reprints, Series 2
  - Allen, J. Garott (Box 10)
  - Allen, Warren D. (Box 10)
  - Allgard, F. Thomas (Box 10)
  - Almack, John L. (Box 10)
  - Almond, Nina (Box 11)
  - Alsberg, C. L., Four bound volumes of reprints 1901-1939 (Box 90)
  - Alsberg, Carl L. (Box 11)
  - Alsberg, Carl S. (Box 11)
  - Anastasiow, Nicholas J. (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Bruce M. (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Henry S. (Box 90)
  - Anderson, John A. (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Melville Best (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Melville Best (Box 90)
  - Anderson, Robert Van Vleck (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Virgil (Box 11)
  - Angell, Frank (Box 11)
  - Anliker, Max (Box 11)
  - Appell, Alfred, Jr. (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Elmer Ivan (Box 11)
  - Armer, Paul (Box 11)
  - Arrow, Kenneth (Box 12)
  - Aschheim, Emil (Box 12)
  - Ashley, Rea E. (Box 12)
  - Atwood, F. J., Capt. (Box 12)
  - Auld, B. A. (Box 12)
  - Baalsrud, K. (Box 12)
  - Bacon, Harold M. (Box 12)
  - Bacon, Robert L. (Box 12)
  - Bacon, Shirley H. (Box 12)
  - Bailey, Margery A. (Box 12)
  - Bailey, Thomas A. (Box 12)
  - Bamman, Henry A. (Box 13)
  - Barahal, George D. (Box 13)
  - Baran, Paul A. (Box 13)
  - Barber, W. C. (Box 13)
  - Barclay, Thomas S. (Box 13)
  - Barkan, Hans (Box 13)
  - Barkan, Otto (Box 13)
  - Barker, Charles A. (Box 13)
  - Barker, Chester Wing (Box 13)
  - Barnes, Earl (Box 13)
  - Barnes, Earl (Box 90)
  - Barnes, Mary Shelton (Box 13)
  - Barnett, S. J. (Box 14)
  - Barr, Richard H. (Box 14)
  - Bassett, David L. (Box 14)
  - Bassett, Lee Emerson (Box 14)
  - Bateman, William G. (Box 14)
  - Bates, Talcott (Box 14)
  - Bateson, G. (Box 14)
  - Baum, Frank G. (Box 14)
  - Baumberger, James Percy (Box 14)
  - Bavelas, Alex (Box 14)
  - Bay, Christian (Box 14)
  - Bayer, Leona M. (Box 14)
  - Beach, Walter G. (Box 14)
  - Beadle, George W. (Box 14)
  - Beals, Alan R. (Box 14)
  - Beard, Paul J. (Box 14)
  - Beard, Rodney R. (Box 14)
  - Becker, G. E. (Box 14)
  - Befu, Harumi (Box 14)
  - Bell, T. F. (Box 14)
  - Bender, J. T. (Box 14)
  - Bennett, M. K. (Box 14)
  - Bentley, R. C. (Box 15)
  - Bergstrom, F. W. (Box 15)
  - Berman, Arthur (Box 15)
  - Bernstein, Donald E. (Box 15)
  - Besseling, J. F. (Box 15)
  - Bestor, Arthur Eugene, Jr. (Box 15)
  - Bevier, George (Box 15)
  - Bingham, Joseph Walter (Box 15)
  - Black, John D. (Box 15)
  - Black, Melvin B. (Box 15)
  - Blackwelder, Eliot (Box 1)
  - Blackwelder, Eliot (Box 2)
  - Blair, John D., Col. (Box 15)
  - Blaisdell, Frank E., Sr. (Box 15)
  - Blaisdell, Frank E., Sr. (cont.) (Box 16)
  - Blenner, Hassett R. (Box 16)
  - Blichfeldt, H. F. (Box 16)
  - Blinks, L. R. (Box 16)
  - Bloch, Felix (Box 16)
  - Blodgett, Benjamin C. (Box 16)
  - Blois, M. S. (Box 16)
  - Blois, Scott (Box 16)
  - Blommfield, Arthur L. (Box 16)
  - Blum, H. L. (Box 16)
  - Blum, Richard (Box 16)
  - Blumberg, Mark S. (Box 16)
  - Bode, Karl (Box 16)
  - Boeninger, Hildegard (Box 16)
  - Bohnsle, R. V. (Box 16)
  - Bolljahn, John T. (Box 16)
  - Bolton, H. E. (Box 16)
  - Bonner, W. A. (Box 17)
  - Borley, W. E (Box 17)
  - Bornet, Vaughn D. (Box 17)
  - Bovill, Edwin G., Jr. (Box 17)
  - Boyan, Norman J. (Box 17)
  - Bracewell, R. N. (Box 17)
  - Bradbury, Norris E. (Box 17)
  - Bradley, Harold Whitman (Box 17)
  - Bradley, Worthen (Box 17)
  - Bradway, Katherine P. (Box 17)
  - Brand, Carl F. (Box 17)
  - Brandt, Karl F. (Box 17)
  - Brasch, Frederick E. (Box 17)
  - Bray, James O. (Box 17)
  - Brean, Henry P. (Box 17)
  - Breidenbach, Warren C. (Box 17)
  - Brice, N M. (Box 17)
  - Briggs, William Dinsmore (Box 17)
  - Briggs, Winslow R. (Box 17)
  - Brower, Robert H. (Box 18)
  - Brown, Bolton Coit (Box 18)
  - Brown, Cabot (Box 18)
  - Brown, Charles R. (Box 18)
  - Brown, Harold Chapman (Box 18)
  - Brown, John Sewall (Box 18)
  - Brown, Joseph G. (Box 18)
  - Brown, Leland H. (Box 18)
  - Brown, Lucy Hatcher (Box 18)
  - Brown, R. Gene (Box 18)
  - Brown, Stephanie (Box 18)
  - Brown, Walter H. (Box 18)
  - Brownson, Orestes A. (Box 18)
  - Brunetti, Cledo (Box 18)
  - Bube, Richard H. (Box 18)
  - Buckingham, Elizabeth (Box 18)
  - Bumiller, F. (Box 19)
  - Bunker, J. P. (Box 19)
  - Bunting, Helen Masters (Box 19)
  - Burdick, William L. (Box 19)
  - Burke, Georgina S. (Box 19)
  - Burkland, Carl E. (Box 19)
  - Burlingame, L. Lancelot (Box 19)
  - Burns, Victor W. (Box 19)
  - Burrell, Florence C. (Box 19)
  - Bush, Chilton R. (Box 19)
  - Buss, Claude A. (Box 19)
  - Byers, N. (Box 19)
  - Byrd, Oliver (Box 19)
  - Cadle, R. D. (Box 19)
  - Cady, Vernon M. (Box 19)
  - Caldwell, William L. (Box 19)
  - Campbell, Douglas H. (Box 19)
  - Canning, John Bennett (Box 19)
  - Cannon, Arthur M. (Box 19)
  - Cannon, Henry Lewis (Box 19)
  - Carlson, Anton Julius (Box 19)
  - Carnes, William H. (Box 19)
  - Carnochan, W. B. (Box 19)
  - Carpenter, Donald L. (Box 19)
  - Carroll, Joseph S. (Box 19)
  - Carruth, William H. (Box 19)
  - Carruth, William Herbert (Box 91)
  - Carter, Richard F. (Box 19)
  - Cathcart, A. M. (Box 19)
  - Cauwet, Ray W. (Box 20)
  - Chamberlain, W. Edward (Box 20)
  - Chamberlain, Waldo (Box 20)
  - Chao, Fu-Chuan (Box 20)
  - Chapin, L. T. (Box 20)
  - Chapman, Gloria (Box 20)
  - Chapman, Seville (Box 20)
  - Charles, Caroline Moore (Box 20)
  - Charters, S. Barclay (Box 91)
  - Chenery, Hollis B. (Box 20)
  - Chernoff, Herman (Box 20)
  - Chilcote, Ronald H. (Box 20)
  - Childs, Alfred (Box 20)
  - Chodorow, Marvin (Box 20)
  - Chope, Harold D. (Box 20)
  - Chu, E. L. (Box 20)
  - Clark, Arthur B. (Box 20)
  - Clark, Birge (Box 20)
  - Clark, Frederick (Box 20)
  - Clark, George Archibald (Box 20)
  - Clark, George T. (Box 20)
  - Clark, Harry (Box 20)
  - Clark, J. C. (Box 20)
  - Clark, W. Dayton (Box 20)
  - Clausen, Jens (Box 20)
  - Clayton, Roderick (Box 20)
  - Clebsch, William (Box 21)
  - Clendenen, Clarence C. (Box 21)
  - Clevenger, Galen (Box 21)
  - Clifton, Charles E. (Box 21)
  - Cline, John (Box 21)
  - Coan, Eugene (Box 21)
  - Coester, Alfred (Box 21)
  - Cohn, Ray (Box 22)
  - Coladarci, Arthur D. (Box 22)
  - Colby, Edward E. (Box 22)
  - Coman, Edwin T. (Box 22)
  - Compton, Ariel S. (Box 22)
  - Compton, Robert R. (Box 22)
  - Comstock, Anna (Box 22)
  - Conolly, John E. (Box 22)
  - Conway, R. W. (Box 22)
  - Cook, Paul M. (Box 22)
  - Coolidge, Mary Roberts Smith (Box 22)
  - Cooper, W. S. (Box 22)
  - Cooper, William Alpha (Box 22)
  - Cope, Oliver (Box 22)
  - Corker, Charles (Box 22)
  - Cotter, Cornelius (Box 22)
  - Cottrell, Edwin A. (Box 22)
  - Coward, D. H. (Box 22)
  - Cowdery, Karl (Box 22)
  - Cowie, Alexander (Box 22)
  - Cowley, W. H. (Box 22)
  - Cox, Alvin J. (Box 3)
  - Cox, Alvin J. (Box 22)
  - Cox, Charles E. (Box 22)
  - Cox, Francis J. (Box 22)
  - Craig, Gordon A. (Box 23)
  - Craig, Hardin (Box 23)
  - Crandall, Berton W. (Box 23)
  - Crandall, Roderic (Box 23)
  - Crawford, Albert (Box 23)
  - Creger, William P. (Box 23)
  - Crisman. Jefferson (Box 23)
  - Croft, T. A. (Box 23)
  - Crook, Welton J. (Box 23)
  - Cross, C. N. (Box 23)
  - Cross, Charles R. (Box 23)
  - Cross, Ira B. (Box 23)
  - Crossland, Paul M. (Box 23)
  - Crothers, Elizabeth Mills (Box 23)
  - Crothers, George Edward (Box 23)
  - Crum, W. L. (Box 23)
  - Crumly, C. B. (Box 23)
  - Culver, George (Box 23)
  - Cummings, Raymond C. (Box 23)
  - Cunningham, J. V. (Box 23)
  - Cuthbertson, E. N. (Box 23)
  - Cuthbertson, Kenneth M. (Box 23)
  - Cutler, Leland W. (Box 24)
  - Cutler, Levern W. (Box 24)
  - Cutting, James A. (Box 24)
  - Cutting, Windsor C. (Box 24)
  - Danforth, C. H. (Box 24)
  - Danton, George Henry (Box 24)
  - Dantzig, George (Box 24)
  - Dasgupta, Partha (Box 24)
  - Davidson, F. J. A. (Box 24)
  - Davidson, Julian M. (Box 24)
  - Davidson, Percy (Box 24)
  - Davis, Albert (Box 24)
  - Davis, Horace (Box 24)
  - Davis, Joseph H. (Box 24)
  - Davis, Joseph S. (Box 24)
  - Davis, Joseph S., [2 speeches] (Box 91)
  - Davis, Joseph S. (cont.) (Box 25)
  - Davis, Paul H. (Box 26)
  - Davis, Stanley N. (Box 26)
  - Davis, William Hawley (Box 26)
  - Davison, Roland A. (Box 26)
  - De Camp, J. E. (Box 26)
  - De Carle, Donald (Box 19)
  - De Eds, Floyd (Box 26)
  - De Lemos, Pedro J. (Box 26)
  - De Vault, D. C. (Box 26)
  - Dean, Bashford (Box 26)
  - Dean, Robert B. (Box 26)
  - Dean, Sanford (Box 26)
  - Dedrick, K. G. (Box 26)
  - Dembo, Tamara (Box 26)
  - Dement, William C. (Box 26)
  - Deming, Quentin B. (Box 26)
  - Demorest, Byron (Box 26)
  - Derfler, Heinrich (Box 26)
  - Dharmatti, S. S. (Box 26)
  - Di Caprio, Joseph M. (Box 26)
  - Dickerson, Mary C. (Box 26)
  - Dickey, Lloyd B. (Box 26)
  - Dickson, Ernest C. (Box 26)
  - Dillon, James (Box 26)
  - Disman, M. I. (Box 26)
  - Disse, Werner (Box 26)
  - Dixon, Richard F. (Box 26)
  - Djerassi, Carl (Box 26)
  - Doane, R. W. (Box 26)
  - Dobson, Leonard (Box 26)
  - Dock, William (Box 26)
  - Dodds, John W. (Box 26)
  - Dodge, Melvin G. (Box 26)
  - Doell, Richard R. (Box 26)
  - Done, Alan (Box 26)
  - Donio, Jean I. (Box 26)
  - Dornbusch, Sanford (Box 26)
  - Dowley, Edith M. (Box 26)
  - Downey, Vincent M. (Box 26)
  - Downing, George C. (Box 26)
  - Dowrie, George (Box 26)
  - Doyle, Anastasia (Box 26)
  - Doyle, T. C. (Box 26)
  - Drell, Sidney D. (Box 27)
  - Ducommun, Charles E. (Box 27)
  - Duniway, C. A. (Box 27)
  - Dunn, D. A. (Box 27)
  - Durand, William F. (Box 27)
  - Eastman, R. W. (Box 27)
  - Eaton, J. M. (Box 27)
  - Ebb, Lawrence F. (Box 27)
  - Eckart, W. R., Jr. (Box 27)
  - Edwards, Paul C. (Box 27)
  - Eells, Walter C. (Box 27)
  - Eisenberg, Max (Box 27)
  - Eisenbraum, E. J. (Box 27)
  - Eldridge, Lynn (Box 27)
  - Eliasen, Rolf (Box 27)
  - Eliel, Paul (Box 27)
  - Elliot (Box 27)
  - Elliot, Orrin Leslie (Box 28)
  - Ellis, Eldon E. (Box 28)
  - Elmore, Jefferson (Box 28)
  - Eloesser, Leo (Box 28)
  - Elrich, Paul R. (Box 28)
  - Elson, Douglas C. (Box 28)
  - Emerson, James Gordon (Box 28)
  - Emge, Ludwig A. (Box 28)
  - Emmet, Boris (Box 28)
  - Engel, Sam (Box 28)
  - Engels, Henry (Box 28)
  - Enright, John B. (Box 28)
  - Epstein, Ervin (Box 28)
  - Erb, Donald M. (Box 28)
  - Erickson, Olive Fedde (Box 28)
  - Eshelman, Von. R. (Box 28)
  - Espinosa, Aurelio M. (Box 28)
  - Espinosa, Aurelio M. (cont.) (Box 29)
  - Estes, W. K. (Box 29)
  - Eudin, Xenia J. (Box 29)
  - Eulau, Heinz (Box 29)
  - Eurich, Alvin C. (Box 29)
  - Evans, Frederick B. (Box 29)
  - Evans, John M. (Box 30)
  - Evans, Luther H. (Box 30)
  - Evans, Robert S. (Box 30)
  - Evans, William E. (Box 30)
  - Evans-Wentz, Walter Y. (Box 30)
  - Everman, Barton W. (Box 30)
  - Ewell, Raymond H. (Box 30)
  - Faber, Harold K. (Box 30)
  - Fagan, Elmer D. (Box 30)
  - Fairclough, H. R. (Box 30)
  - Fan, Stephen S. T. (Box 30)
  - Farnsworth, Helen C. (Box 30)
  - Farnsworth, Paul R. (Box 30)
  - Farrand, Max (Box 30)
  - Faville, David E. (Box 30)
  - Favour, C. B. (Box 31)
  - Fearing, F. S. (Box 31)
  - Feferman, Solomon (Box 31)
  - Fehrenbacher, D. E. (Box 31)
  - Feigelson, Robert S. (Box 31)
  - Feigen, George (Box 31)
  - Feigen, Gerald M. (Box 31)
  - Feldman, Daniel J. (Box 31)
  - Fender, Frederick (Box 31)
  - Fenton, Norman (Box 31)
  - Ferguson, Lucy Rau (see also Lucy Rau) (Box 31)
  - Ferris, Gordon Floyd (Box 31)
  - Fertman, Mildred B. (Box 31)
  - Fetter, Frank A. (Box 31)
  - Field, John II (Box 31)
  - Fiese, Marshall J. (Box 32)
  - Fifer, C. N. (Box 32)
  - Findlay, Alexander (Box 32)
  - Fine, Max (Box 32)
  - Finley, Knox H. (Box 32)
  - Fish, J. C. L. (Box 32)
  - Fisher, Harold (Box 32)
  - Fisher, Walter K. (Box 32)
  - Fleeman, J. (Box 32)
  - Flocks, Milton (Box 32)
  - Flugel, Ewald (Box 33)
  - Fondahl, John W. (Box 33)
  - Font, John (Box 33)
  - Ford, Newell F. (Box 33)
  - Forgy, Edward W. (Box 33)
  - Forman, Lewis W. (Box 33)
  - Forsythe, George E. (Box 33)
  - Foster, Benjamin O. (Box 33)
  - Foster, Jean A. (Box 33)
  - Frank, Arthur L. (Box 33)
  - Frank, Peter (Box 33)
  - Frankel, Herman (Box 33)
  - Frankel, Theodore (Box 33)
  - Franklin, Edward Curtis (Box 33)
  - Franklin, Edward Curtis (cont.) (Box 34)
  - Franklin, W. S. (Box 34)
  - Franzini, Joseph B. (Box 34)
  - Freeman, Norman E. (Box 34)
  - Freeman, Roger A. (Box 34)
  - Freidman, Meyer (Box 34)
  - French, C. S. (Box 34)
  - Frerichs, John B. (Box 34)
  - Friedel, Frank (Box 34)
  - Friedlander, Walter J. (Box 34)
  - Friedman, Milton (Box 34)
  - Fry, William F. (Box 34)
  - Fuhrman, N. Howell (Box 34)
  - Furst, Arthur (Box 34)
  - Gardner, David Charles (Box 34)
  - Gardner, John W. (Box 34)
  - Gardner, Kenneth D., Jr. (Box 34)
  - Garland, L. Henry (Box 34)
  - Garland, L. Henry (cont.) (Box 35)
  - Garriot, Owen K. (Box 35)
  - Garvias, V. R. (Box 35)
  - Gault, Charles A. (Box 35)
  - Gebhart, L. P. (Box 35)
  - Geiger, J. C. (Box 35)
  - Geraci, Charles L. (Box 35)
  - Gerathewohl, Siegfried J. (Box 35)
  - Gerbode, Frank (Box 35)
  - Gere, James M. (Box 35)
  - Germane, Gayton E. (Box 35)
  - Germann, Albert F. O. (Box 35)
  - Gerould, Albert C. (Box 35)
  - Gerstl, Bruno (Box 35)
  - Gibbons, Henry, III (Box 35)
  - Gibbons, Henry, Sr. (Box 35)
  - Gibbons, James F. (Box 35)
  - Gibson, Weldon B. (Box 35)
  - Giese, A. C. (Box 35)
  - Gilbert, Charles H. (Box 35)
  - Gilbert, Charles H. (cont.) (Box 36)
  - Gilfillian, R. S. (Box 36)
  - Ginzton, Edward L. (Box 36)
  - Glover, Frederick O. (Box 36)
  - Goebel, Julius (Box 36)
  - Goertz, David J. (Box 36)
  - Goetz, A. A. (Box 36)
  - Goetzel, Claus G. (Box 36)
  - Goheen, John O. (Box 36)
  - Goldberg, Moses H. (Box 36)
  - Golder, Frank A. (Box 36)
  - Good, Edwin M. (Box 37)
  - Gorman, William A. (Box 37)
  - Graham, J. J. (Box 37)
  - Grambs, Jean (Box 37)
  - Granger, J. V. N. (Box 37)
  - Grannis, William R. (Box 37)
  - Grant, Eugene L. (Box 37)
  - Grant, Joseph (Box 37)
  - Grant, Ronald (Box 37)
  - Grass, Donald (Box 37)
  - Gray, Henry David (Box 37)
  - Gray, Horace (Box 37)
  - Gray, Roger W. (Box 37)
  - Green, Rufus L. (Box 37)
  - Green, T. M. (Box 37)
  - Greene, W. Wallace (Box 37)
  - Greulich, William W. (Box 37)
  - Grey, David L. (Box 37)
  - Grey, Thomas Cunningham (Box 37)
  - Gribble, Terence John (Box 37)
  - Grieder, Elmer M. (Box 37)
  - Gries, David (Box 37)
  - Griffen, Paul A. (Box 37)
  - Griffin, A. C. (Box 38)
  - Griffin, James O. (Box 38)
  - Griffin, Jerry C. (Box 38)
  - Griffin, Paul A. (Box 38)
  - Griffin, Paul F. (Box 38)
  - Griffing, Elizabeth P. (Box 38)
  - Griffith, J. S. (Box 38)
  - Griffith, Samuel B. (Box 38)
  - Griffiths, D. J. (Box 38)
  - Griffy, Thomas A. (Box 38)
  - Griggs, Edward H. (Box 38)
  - Grinnell, Robert (Box 38)
  - Grinnell, S. W. (Box 38)
  - Grobstein, Clifford (Box 38)
  - Grojean, G. H. (Box 38)
  - Grommon, Alfred Harvey (Box 38)
  - Gross, Richard E. (Box 38)
  - Gross, Ruth T. (Box 38)
  - Grossman, Maurice (Box 38)
  - Grossman, Sanford J. (Box 38)
  - Guerard, Albert J. (Box 38)
  - Guerard, Albert L. (Box 38)
  - Gugelot, P. C. (Box 38)
  - Gunn, Herbert (Box 38)
  - Guthrie, Luell Weed ( see Luell Weed)
  - Hagen, John W. (Box 38)
  - Hahn, E. L. (Box 38)
  - Haldi, John (Box 38)
  - Haley, Jay (Box 38)
  - Hall, Howard Judson (Box 38)
  - Hall, Lewis D. (Box 38)
  - Hall, Victor E. (Box 38)
  - Halter, Bert L. (Box 38)
  - Haman, John O. (Box 38)
  - Hammond, Richard J. (Box 38)
  - Hamrdla, G. Robert (Box 38)
  - Hanan, Patrick Dewes (Box 38)
  - Hanawalt, Philip C. (Box 39)
  - Hancock, Moffatt (Box 39)
  - Hand, Harold C. (Box 39)
  - Hanna, Paul R. (Box 39)
  - Hansen, W. W. (Box 39)
  - Hanzlik, Paul J. (Box 39)
  - Harbough, John W. (Box 39)
  - Hardwick, R. (Box 39)
  - Harlow, Rex F. (Box 39)
  - Harman, W. W. (Box 39)
  - Harrell, Thomas W. (Box 39)
  - Harrington, G. L. (Box 39)
  - Harris, Christina Z. (Box 39)
  - Harris, David (Box 39)
  - Harris, Morgan (Box 39)
  - Harris, S. Dale (Box 39)
  - Harris, William J. (Box 39)
  - Harrison, George R. (Box 39)
  - Harrison, Ross G. (Box 39)
  - Hartman, Milton M. (Box 40)
  - Hastorf, Albert H. (Box 40)
  - Haxo, Frances T. (Box 40)
  - Hayden, Carl (Box 40)
  - Haydon, Glen B. (Box 40)
  - Hays, Alice Newman (Box 40)
  - Heath, Harold (Box 40)
  - Heck, Walter E. (Box 40)
  - Heer, Nicholas L. (Box 40)
  - Heffner, Hubert (Box 40)
  - Heffner, Hubert C. (Box 40)
  - Helliwell, Robert A. (Box 40)
  - Hempl, George (Box 40)
  - Henline, Henry H. (Box 40)
  - Hepp, Virgil E. (Box 40)
  - Herre, Albert W.C.T. (Box 4)
  - Herre, Albert W.C.T. (Box 5)
  - Herriot, John G. (Box 40)
  - Hetherington, Clark W. (Box 40)
  - Hilgard, Ernest R. (Box 41)
  - Hilgard, Josephine (Box 41)
  - Hillier, Frederick S. (Box 41)
  - Hilton, Ronald (Box 41)
  - Hodges, Charles (Box 41)
  - Hoover, Theodore T. (Box 41)
  - Isenberg, Arnold (Box 41)
  - Jackson, Don D. (Box 42)
  - Jackson, J. Hugh (Box 42)
  - Jacobs, Alvin H. (Box 42)
  - Jacobsen, L. S. (Box 42)
  - Jacobson, David S. (Box 42)
  - James, Maud Merrill (Box 42)
  - James, William (missing, paged) (Box 42)
  - Jamison, Dean (Box 42)
  - Jamplis, Robert W. (Box 42)
  - Jampolsky, Arthur (Box 42)
  - Jasny, Naum (Box 42)
  - Jaynes, Edwin T. (Box 42)
  - Jeffries, C. D. (Box 42)
  - Jenkins, Olaf P. (Box 42)
  - Jenkins, Oliver P. (Box 42)
  - Jensen, Barry T. (Box 42)
  - Jernigan, J. A. (Box 42)
  - Johns, Ned B. (Box 44)
  - Johnson, Francis R. (Box 42)
  - Johnson, John J. (Box 43)
  - Johnson, Phillips (Box 43)
  - Johnson, W. H. (Box 43)
  - Johnson, William S. (Box 43)
  - Johnston, Bruce F. (Box 43)
  - Johnston, Oliver M. (Box 43)
  - Jones, Eliot (Box 44)
  - Jones, Robert (Box 44)
  - Jones, William O. (Box 44)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 44)
  - Joseph, Herbert L. (Box 44)
  - Jungeblut, Claus W. (Box 44)
  - Just, Evan (Box 44)
  - Kaiser, A. D. (Box 44)
  - Kallman, Robert F. (Box 44)
  - Kalman, Sumner M. (Box 44)
  - Kanellakos, D. P. (Box 44)
  - Kaplan, Henry S. (Box 44)
  - Karzmark, C. J. (Box 44)
  - Katz, Lilian (Box 44)
  - Kaulfers, Walter V. (Box 44)
  - Keen, A. Myra (Box 44)
  - Keen, A. Myra (cont.) (Box 45)
  - Keesing, Felix M. (Box 45)
  - Kefauver, Grayson N. (Box 45)
  - Kelley, Kenneth (Box 45)
  - Kelley, Truman L. (Box 45)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. (Box 45)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. (cont.) (Box 46)
  - Kelly, Robert G. (Box 46)
  - Kendall, Willmoore (Box 46)
  - Kennedy, Arthur G. (Box 46)
  - Kennedy, John L. (Box 47)
  - Kennedy, W. R. (Box 47)
  - Kieran, James (Box 47)
  - Kimberly, James C. (Box 47)
  - Kimpton, L. A. (Box 47)
  - Kinney, Lucien B. (Box 47)
  - Kirby, William M. M. (Box 47)
  - Kirk, Dudley (Box 47)
  - Kirkman, Hadley (Box 47)
  - Kirkpatrick, Paul (Box 47)
  - Kirkwood, Marion R. (Box 47)
  - Klausner, Claire (Box 47)
  - Kline, Stephen J. (Box 47)
  - Klotter, K. (Box 48)
  - Knapp, Maud L. (Box 48)
  - Knight, Kenneth E. (Box 48)
  - Knoles, George Harmon (Box 48)
  - Knopf, Adolph (Box 48)
  - Knorr, K. E. (Box 48)
  - Koenig, F. O. (Box 48)
  - Koets, Peter (Box 48)
  - Kohlmoos, Heinrich (Box 48)
  - Kohs, Samuel C. (Box 48)
  - Kolb, Leon (Box 48)
  - Konrad, Karl W. (Box 48)
  - Kornberg, Arthur (Box 48)
  - Krasner, Leonard (Box 48)
  - Krassovsky, Dimitry M. (Box 48)
  - Krehbiel, Edward B. (Box 48)
  - Kreps, Theodore J. (Box 48)
  - Krieger, George (Box 49)
  - Kriss, Joseph (Box 49)
  - Krueger, A. P. (Box 49)
  - Kruger, Paul (Box 49)
  - Krupp, Marcus A. (Box 49)
  - Kulchar, George V. (Box 49)
  - Kurz, Mordecai (Box 49)
  - Kuzell, William C. (Box 49)
  - La Piere, Richard T. (Box 49)
  - La Plante, John D. (Box 49)
  - Lamson, David A. (Box 49)
  - Landauer, Thomas K. (Box 49)
  - Langmuir, Gavin I. (Box 49)
  - Langnecker, H. L. (Box 49)
  - Lanz, Henry (Box 49)
  - Larsen, Helge (Box 49)
  - Lau, Lawrence Juen-Yee (Box 49)
  - Laurie, Victor (Box 49)
  - Lawson, A. A. (Box 49)
  - Leavelle, Arnaud B. (Box 49)
  - Lederberg, E. M. (Box 49)
  - Lederberg, Joshua (Box 49)
  - Lee, Erastus H. (Box 50)
  - Lee, George Q. (Box 50)
  - Lee, Lamar, Jr. (Box 50)
  - Lee, Philip R. (Box 50)
  - Lee, Russell V. A. (Box 50)
  - Leeds, M. Fredrick (Box 50)
  - Leggo, Christopher (Box 50)
  - Lehman, A. J. (Box 50)
  - Leighton, Philip A. (Box 50)
  - Leland, Hayne E. (Box 50)
  - Lenkey, Susan V. (Box 50)
  - Leppert, G. (Box 50)
  - Levin, David (Box 50)
  - Levine, Harold (Box 50)
  - Levine, Seymour (Box 50)
  - Levinthal, E. C. (Box 50)
  - Levorsen, A. I. (Box 50)
  - Lewis, J. K. (Box 50)
  - Lewis, Janet (Box 50)
  - Lhamon, Ruskin M. (Box 50)
  - Lieberman, Gerald J. (Box 50)
  - Liljencrantz, Eric (Box 50)
  - Lincoln, Charles (Box 50)
  - Lindsley, David F. (Box 50)
  - Linsley, R. K. (Box 50)
  - Linvill, John G. (Box 50)
  - Lion, Ernest G. (Box 50)
  - Little, Kenneth B. (Box 50)
  - Little, William A. (Box 50)
  - Littlefield, Edmund W. (Box 50)
  - Loewner, Charles (Box 50)
  - Loftis, John (Box 50)
  - London, A. L. (Box 51)
  - Long, Albert E. (Box 51)
  - Loring, Hubert S. (Box 51)
  - Lougee, Carolyn (Box 51)
  - Lovejoy, Arthur O. (Box 51)
  - Lowenstein, Jerold M. (Box 51)
  - Lowrence, Edward W. (Box 51)
  - Lubin, Albert J. (Box 51)
  - Luck, James Murray (Box 51)
  - Luckett, George S. (Box 51)
  - Luduena, F. P. (Box 51)
  - Luft, Joseph (Box 51)
  - Lusignan, Bruce B. (Box 51)
  - Luth, W. C. (Box 51)
  - Luther, C. F. (Box 51)
  - Luthy, Nydia G. (Box 51)
  - Luttgens, William S. (Box 51)
  - Lutz, Harley L. (Box 51)
  - Lutz, Ralph H. (Box 51)
  - Lyman, George D. (Box 52)
  - Lynch, Edward J. (Box 52)
  - Maccoby, Eleanor E. (Box 52)
  - Maccoby, Nathan (Box 52)
  - MacDonald, John D. (Box 52)
  - MacFarland, Frank Mace (Box 52)
  - MacGinitie, G. E. (Box 52)
  - MacKay, Donald C. G. (Box 52)
  - Madden, Henry M. (Box 52)
  - Madding, Gordon F. (Box 52)
  - Maffly, Roy H. (Box 52)
  - Magaret, Ann (Box 52)
  - Magill, Paul L. (Box 52)
  - Mahr, August C. (Box 52)
  - Majumdar, Mukul (Box 52)
  - Mandel, Arthur A. (Box 52)
  - Mann, J. Keith (Box 52)
  - Manning, Bayless (Box 52)
  - Manning, L. A. (Box 52)
  - Manning, William A. (Box 52)
  - Manwaring, William H. (Box 53)
  - Margolis, Julius (Box 53)
  - Margulies, Gerald S. (Box 53)
  - Marr, John C. (Box 53)
  - Marshall, Hubert (Box 53)
  - Martin, Charles E. (Box 53)
  - Martin, E. G. (Box 53)
  - Martin, L. H. (Box 53)
  - Martin, Lillien Jane (Box 53)
  - Martin, Percy A. (Box 53)
  - Martin, Percy A. (cont.) (Box 54)
  - Marton, L. (Box 54)
  - Maruyama, Magoroh (Box 54)
  - Marx, Guido (Box 54)
  - Mary, Charles D. (Box 54)
  - Masland, J. W. (Box 54)
  - Mason, David M. (Box 54)
  - Masters, Alfred K. (Box 54)
  - Mathewson, Carleton, Jr. (Box 54)
  - Mathison, John K. (Box 54)
  - Matzke, John E. (Box 54)
  - Maxmin, Jody (Box 55)
  - Mazour, Anatole G. (Box 55)
  - McAnear, Beverly (Box 55)
  - McBain, James W. (Box 55)
  - McCarthy, John (Box 55)
  - McCarty, Perry L. (Box 55)
  - McClain, Emlin (Box 55)
  - McCracken, Isabel (Box 55)
  - McEwan, George F. (Box 55)
  - McLean, Philip T. (Box 55)
  - McLean, S. J. (Box 55)
  - McNaught, James B. (Box 55)
  - McNaught, Robert C. (Box 55)
  - McNemar, Quinn (Box 55)
  - Meadows, Gail K. (Box 56)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell (Box 56)
  - Meiburg, Charles O. (Box 56)
  - Meier, E. (Box 56)
  - Meininger, Willard M. (Box 56)
  - Mendelwitz, Daniel (Box 56)
  - Mensor, Merrill C. (Box 56)
  - Merryman, John H. (Box 56)
  - Meyer, Arthur W. (Box 57)
  - Meyerhof, W. E. (Box 57)
  - Meyers, Charles J. (Box 57)
  - Michelson, Lewis (Box 57)
  - Michelson, Robin P. (Box 57)
  - Miles, Catherine Cox (Box 57)
  - Miles, Walter R. (Box 58)
  - Miller, Alexander (Box 58)
  - Miller, Frank G. (Box 59)
  - Miller, John M. (Box 59)
  - Miller, Walter (Box 59)
  - Mills, H. A. (Box 59)
  - Miracle, Marvin (Box 59)
  - Mitchell, Harold (Box 59)
  - Mitchell, J. P. (Box 59)
  - Moll, J. L. (Box 59)
  - Monroe, Will S. (Box 59)
  - Moody, Graham B. (Box 59)
  - Moos, Rudolf H. (Box 59)
  - Morgan, Bayard Q. (Box 59)